Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Don Waters, 1987-1993; Accession 2000-A-013
  - ORBIS (Box 6)
    - Budget (Box 6)
      - Presentation (Box 6)
      - Projections, 1990 (Box 6)
      - Projections, 1991 (Box 6)
      - Proposal, 1987 October (Box 6)
      - Proposal, 1988 January (Box 6)
        - Addendum 1 (Box 6)
    - Budget Analysis (Box 6)
      - Spring 1992 (Box 6)
      - Spring 1993 (Box 6)
      - Spring 1994 (Box 6)
    - Call List (Box 6)
    - Capacity Summary Report (Box 6)
    - CICS Overview (Box 7)
    - Circulation (Box 7)
      - Barcodes (Box 7)
      - Backup System (Box 7)
      - Bursar's Tape (Box 7)
      - Support Group (Box 7)
    - Coordinating Group (OCG) (Box 7)
      - Minutes (Box 7)
      - Networked Information Support Group (Box 7)
      - OPAC (Box 7)
      - Workstation Task Force (Box 7)
    - Cost Information Sheet (Box 7)
    - DASD Performance (Box 7)
    - DASD Requirements (Box 7)
    - Database IYfaintenance (Box 7)
    - Database Planning (Box 7)
    - Database Statistics (Box 7)
    - Electronic Invoices (Box 7)
    - Equipment (Box 7)
      - 7171 (Box 7)
      - Maintenance (Box 7)
      - Orders (Box 7)
      - Security (Box 7)
    - Evaluation (Box 7)
    - Expenses, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
    - Label Printing (Box 7)
    - Machine Purchase Price (Box 7)
    - Mystery Series (Box 7)
      - Timetable (Box 7)
    - OPAC Support Group (Box 7)
    - OPAC Working Group (Box 7)
    - Presentation to CIS (Box 7)
    - Pricing (Box 7)
    - Security (Box 7)
  - Ordering Books for Departments (Box 7)
  - Peabody Museum (Box 7)
    - Annual Report (Box 7)
    - Argus (Box 7)
  - Position Control (Box 7)
  - Project Open Book (Box 7)
    - Budget (Box 7)
    - Cataloging Issues (Box 7)
    - Contacts (Box 7)
    - Cost Analysis (Box 7)
    - DEC Proposal (Box 7)
    - DEC Requirements Analysis - Contract (Box 7)
    - Document Structure (Box 7)
    - Equipment Maintenance (Box 7)
    - Funding (Box 7)
    - General Proposal and Budget (Box 7)
    - KECK Foundation Proposal (Box 7)
    - NEB Proposal (Box 7)
    - Notes on Issues (Box 7)
    - Organizational Phase (Box 7)
    - Phase I (Box 7)
      - DEC Requirements Analysis (Box 7)
      - Report, Draft (Box 7)
      - Xerox Requirements Analysis (Box 7)
      - Xerox Yale Meeting, 1991 September (Box 7)
    - Phase II (Box 7)
      - Contract (Box 7)
      - Proposal (Box 7)
    - Press Release (Box 7)
    - Production Conversion (Box 7)
      - Equipment (Box 7)
      - Extension (Box 7)
      - Final Report (Box 7)
      - Handbook (Box 7)
      - Interim Report (Box 7)
      - Personnel (Box 7)
      - Press Release (Box 7)
      - Proposal (Box 8)
      - Selection (Box 8)
    - Proposals, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Requests for Proposals, 1991 July (Box 8)
    - Setup Phase (Box 8)
      - Final Report (Box 8)
    - Steering Committee (Box 8)
    - WWW Server (Box 8)
    - Xerox Product Offering (Box 8)
    - Xerox Requirements Analysis - Contract (Box 8)
    - Xerox Contract (Box 8)
  - Project Scholar (Box 8)
  - Stanford University - Technical Services Reorganization (Box 8)
  - Sterling Memorial Library (SML) (Box 8)
    - Doors (Box 8)
    - Fire Alarm Procedures (Box 8)
    - High Street Renovation (Box 8)
    - HVAC (Box 8)
    - Master Plan (Box 8)
    - Nave (Box 8)
    - Renovation (Box 8)
      - Documentation (Box 8)
      - Maps (Box 8)
      - Moves (Box 8)
      - Office Space (Box 8)
      - Painting (Box 8)
      - Project Management (Box 8)
      - Project Minutes (Box 8)
      - Preservation (Box 8)
      - Reading Room (Box 8)
      - Safety (Box 8)
      - Signage (Box 8)
    - Roof (Box 8)
    - Room 3 (Box 8)
    - Room 27 (Box 8)
    - Space Planning (Box 8)
    - Telecommunications (Box 8)
  - Strategic Partnership (Box 8)
  - Strike Contingency Planning (Box 8)
  - Student Admin Services Improvement Project (SASIP) (Box 8)
  - Summer Projects, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Systems Office (Box 8)
    - Action Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 8)
    - Annual Report (Box 8)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 8)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 8)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 8)
      - 1991 (Box 8)
    - Database Administration (Box 8)
    - Mission and Goals (Box 8)
    - Online Texts (Box 8)
    - Primary Contacts (Box 8)
    - Priorities (Box 8)
    - Staff (Box 8)
      - Agenda (Box 8)
      - Development (Box 8)
      - Organization (Box 8)
      - Performance evaluations (Box 8)
        - FY 87/88 (Box 8)
        - 1990 (Box 8)
        - 1991 (Box 8)
        - Apr 1992 (Box 8)
        - 1992 (Box 8)
      - Personnel (Box 8)
        - Coffey, John (Box 8)
      - Requirements (Box 9)
        - Assistant to Head (Box 9)
        - Data - Process - Supt - Technician (Box 9)
        - Documentation Specialist (Box 9)
        - NOTIS Programmer (Box 9)
        - Senior Applications Specialist (Box 9)
        - Senior Programmer Analyst I (Box 9)
        - University Job Descriptions (Box 9)
        - User Support Specialist (Box 9)
      - Salary Structure (Box 9)
    - Vehicle Use (Box 9)
  - Task Force on Digital Archiving - LIBER Conference, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Task Force on Digital Archiving - Luxembourg Trip, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Teaching and Learning (2) (Box 9)
    - Presentation, Fall 1996 (Box 9)
  - UC Berkeley (Box 9)
    - Finding Aids Project (Box 9)
    - Social Sciences (Box 9)
  - United Nations Studies (Box 9)
  - University Council Committee on Information Technology (Box 9)
  - Verancular Scripts (Box 9)
  - Visitors, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Visitors, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
  - Ward and Associates (Box 9)
  - Web Advisory Group (Box 9)
  - Working Group on Off-Campus Shelving (Box 9)
  - World Wide Web (WWW) (Box 9)
    - Yale (Box 9)
      - Library (Box 9)
      - Task Force (Box 9)
  - Xerox (Box 9)
    - Advisory Group (Box 9)
    - Digital Library (Box 9)
    - Digital Solutions Conference, 1994 December (Box 9)
      - Talk (Box 9)
    - Ed Pubs Minutes (Box 9)
    - General (Box 9)
    - Integrated Publishing (Box 9)
    - Print Manager (Box 9)
    - WWWW server (Box 9)
  - Yale College (Box 10)
    - Bluebook (Box 10)
    - Dean's Office Publications Committee (Box 10)
  - Yale Graduate School - Kutzinski Report (Box 10)
  - Yaleinfo (Box 10)
  - Yale University (Box 10)
    - Budget Committee - Subcommittee on Computing (Box 10)
    - Calendar (Box 10)
    - COFRE Study (Box 10)
    - Council Committee Library - Presentation, 1993 June 7 (Box 10)
    - Financial Systems (Box 10)
    - Grants Information (Box 10)
    - Guidelines on Cooperative Exchanges of Info (Box 10)
    - New Haven Initiatives (Box 10)
    - Operating Capital Budgets (Box 10)
    - Post Graduation Study (Box 10)
    - Provost's Ad Hoc Committee (Box 10)
    - Provost's responsibilities (Box 10)
    - Salary Structure (Box 10)
    - Staff (Box 10)
    - Subcommittee on Academic Computing (Box 10)
    - Strike Contingency (Box 10)
    - Technology Vision (Box 10)
    - Yale College Enrollments (Box 10)
  - Yale University Library (Box 10)
    - Advisory Committee on Library Automation (Box 10)
    - Automation (Box 10)
      - General (Box 10)
      - Priorities (Box 10)
    - Committees (Box 10)
    - Directions (Box 10)
    - Director's Briefings, Fall 1994 (Box 10)
    - Issues, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Mission Goals and Objectives (Box 10)
    - Personnel Office (Box 10)
    - Privileges (Box 10)
    - Promotion Review Programs for Librarians (Box 10)
    - Renovation Needs (Box 10)
    - Staff (Box 10)
      - Lori Bronars (Box 10)
      - Linnard Inabinet (Box 10)
      - Monty Montee (Box 10)
      - Louis Silverstein (Box 10)
      - Lou Volpi (Box 10)
    - Status Report, 1993 September (Box 10)
    - Strategic Planning, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Student Employment (Box 10)
    - Task Force on Acquiring Software for Patrons (Box 10)
- Integrated Technical Services and Systems records of Donald Waters, 1983-1995; Accession 2000-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2030
  - ASIS (Box 1)
  - Association of American Publishers (Box 1)
  - Bernstein Project Advisory Council (Box 1)
  - Buy in New Haven Program (Box 1)
  - Capital Maintenance Program (Box 1)
  - Cataloger's Workstation (Box 1)
  - Cataloging Department (Box 1)
    - Cataloger's Forum (Box 1)
    - Orientation Program, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Revision (Box 1)
    - Support Group (Box 1)
    - Team Leader Meetings (Box 1)
    - Working Group (Box 1)
  - CD-ROM (Box 1)
    - DXS (Box 1)
    - Making Your Own (Box 1)
    - Silverplatter (Box 1)
  - Chadwyck-Healey (Box 1)
  - Charlotte Seminar (Box 1)
    - Talk (Box 1)
    - 1995 (Box 1)
  - Chemist's Crystal Ball (CCB) (Box 1)
    - MLA article (Box 1)
    - Paper Draft (Box 1)
    - Survey, 1990 August (Box 1)
  - CJK Automation Task Force (Box 1)
  - Coalition for Networked Information (CNI) (Box 1)
    - Spring 1994 (Box 1)
    - Fall 1994 (Box 1)
    - Spring 1995 (Box 1)
    - Fall 1995 (Box 1)
- Records of Donald Waters as Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, circa 1990-1992; Accession 2006-A-091
  - Vendor files, printed reports, and Yale Open Book Project reports, circa 1990-1992 (Box 1–2)
- Subject files of Donald Waters, circa 1993-1997; Accession 2010-A-054
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - A - Budget (D), circa 1993-1997 (Box 1)
  - Budget (E) - Digital Library, circa 1993-1997 (Box 2)
  - Digital Library - OCLC, circa 1993-1997 (Box 3)
  - OCLC - Preservation (A), circa 1993-1997 (Box 4)
  - Preservation (B - Sp), circa 1993-1997 (Box 5)
  - Preservation (Sp) - Retrospective Conversion, circa 1993-1997 (Box 6)
  - Retrospective Conversion - Social Science Library, circa 1993-1997 (Box 7)
  - Social Science Library - Travel Policy, circa 1993-1997 (Box 8)
- Meg Bellinger files concerning the Visual Resources Collection (VRC), 2004-2007; Accession 2010-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
- Administrative files, circa 1977-1995; Accession 2010-A-056
  Scope and Contents
  consists of annual reports and budget files
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - Administrative files, circa 1977-1995 (Box 1)
  - Administrative files (cont'd), circa 1977-1995 (Box 2)